Jacques Seligmann & Co.
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1913-1978, Series 1:; (80 linear feet)
  - General Correspondence, 1913-1978, 1.3:
    - Charpentier, Thérèse, 1961-1967 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Chatain, Alfred, 1923-1925 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Chatain, Alfred, 1926-1928 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Chatfield-Taylor, Mrs. Robert, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Chatham, Richard Thurmond, 1930-1936 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Chattanooga Art Association, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Chauveau, René, 1947-1956 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Chemical Bank and Trust Co., 1943-1945 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Cheney, Warren, 1934 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Chenue, J., 1926-1933 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Chenue, J., 1934-1935 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Chenue, J., 1936-1939 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Chenue, J., 1940-1949 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Chenue, J., 1950-1953 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Chicago Slide Co., 1934 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Chicago Tribune Ocean Times, 1925 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Chipman, Murray, 1937-1938 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Chirico, Giorgio de (see de Chirico, Giorgio) (Box 21)
    - Chittenden, William J., 1928 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Choate, Mabel, 1925-1948 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Christian Science Monitor, 1951-1953 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Christie, Manson & Woods, Ltd. (Christie's), 1928-1939 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Christie, Manson & Woods, Ltd. (Christie's), 1940-1955 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Christie, Manson & Woods, Ltd. (Christie's), 1956-1958 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Christie, Manson & Woods, Ltd. (Christie's), 1959 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Christie, Manson & Woods, Ltd. (Christie's), 1960-1963 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Christie, Manson & Woods, Ltd. (Christie's), 1964-1970 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Christie, Manson & Woods, Ltd. (Christie's), 1971-1975 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Chrysler, Walter P., Jr., 1927-1959 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Cieslak, Judith, 1956-1966 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Cincinnati, Ohio (Visits and Contacts), circa 1944-1945 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Cintas, Honorable Oscar B., 1940-1950 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Claas, Peter, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Clapp, Willard M., 1923-1926 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Clark, Anthony M., 1958-1961 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Clark, Mr. and Mrs. Charles W., 1921-1948 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Clark, Mrs. Frederick G., 1938-1947 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Clark, G.H.J., 1928-1934 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Clark, Mr. and Mrs. J. W., 1924-1926 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Clark, Sir Kenneth, 1934-1952 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Clark, Melville, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Clark, Robert Sterling, 1940-1956 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Clark, Stephen C., 1924-1958 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Clark, Mr. and Mrs. William A., 1912-1948 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Clarke, John Lee, Jr., 1943-1970 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Clarkson, Grosvenor B., 1924-1930 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Clarkson, Mrs. Robert, 1925-1948 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Clement-Carpeaux, Mme. L., 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Clowes, Dr. G.H.A., 1938-1957 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Coburn, Mrs. Lewis L., 1924-1931 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Cochin, Denys, 1959-1969 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Cochran, Gifford A., 1929-1935 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Cochran, Gifford, 1936-1967 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Cocteau, Jean, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Coe, Ralph M., 1924-1950 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Coe, W. R. (includes Coe Foundation), 1922-1924 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Coe, W. R. (includes Coe Foundation), 1925-1959 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Cohen, Mr. and Mrs. L. Lewis, 1933-1938 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Cohen, Mrs. Max, 1925-1927 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Cohen, William, 1967-1971 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Colin, Ralph F., 1946-1966 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Colle, Pierre, 1945-1946 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - College Art Association, 1931-1938 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - College Art Association, 1945-1972 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Colnaghi & Co., Ltd. (see P. & D. Colnaghi & Co., Ltd.) (Box 23)
    - Combe, Jacques, 1950-1953 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Commissaires Priseurs, 1959-1974 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Conan Doyle, Denis P. S., 1941-1943 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Cone, Etta, 1934-1947 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Conger, Dr. G. T., 1962-1963 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Conley, John E., 1923-1925 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Connaisance des Arts, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Connoisseur, 1924-1953 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Constable, W. G., 1939-1970 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Constantini, Countess, 1924-1926 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Consulat Général de France, 1924-1945 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Contini-Bonacossi, Count Augusto, 1969-1971 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Conzett & Huber, 1953-1954 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Cook Collection, 1939-1943, 1950-1952 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Cook, Robert, 1956-1957 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Cooke, Mrs. Clarence, 1924-1929 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Cooke, Mrs. Theodore, 1925-1928 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Cooney, Mrs. J. Patrick, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Cooper, Douglas, 1936-1969 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Coppet, André de (see de Coppet, André) (Box 24)
    - Cornillot, Marie-Lucie, 1952-1976 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Cortissoz, Royal, 1924-1935 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Costikyan & Co., Inc., 1936 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Cote, Mme. Claudius and Jean, 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Cotton, Leslie, 1928-1935 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Countiss, Mrs. Frederick, 1924-1925 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Courtais, Henri G., 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Courvoisier Galleries, 1933-1939 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Coward, Noel, 1929-1938 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Cowles, Alfred, 1945-1947 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Cox, Atilla, 1925-1927 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Cox, Rev. Robert E., 1947-1948 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Cox-McCormack, Nancy, 1924-1928 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Cramer, Ambrose, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Cramer, S. S., 1947-1949 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Crane, Mrs. Richard T., Jr., 1923-1926 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Crane, Mrs. W. Murray, 1925-1944 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Crawford, Mrs. George, 1940-1948 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Creange, Henry, 1927-1940 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Creative Art, 1928-1933 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Creigton, A. M., 1928-1929 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Cret, Paul Phillippe, 1923-1941 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Crocker, Templeton, 1927-1939 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Crocker, Mrs. W. H., 1926-1929 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Crocker, William W., 1938-1943 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Crosby, Percy, 1934 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Crosby, Percy, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Crosby, Percy, 1936-1945 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Crosby, William H., 1925-1929 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Cross, Mrs. John, 1935-1948 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Crowe & Co., Ltd., 1955-1956 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Crowninshield, Frank, 1932-1947 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Cue, 1936-1959 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Cuevas, Marquis George de (see de Cuevas, Marquis George) (Box 25)
    - Cukor, George, 1936-1941 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Cunard Steam Ship Co., Ltd., 1924-1928 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Cunningham, John J., 1950 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Cunningham, John J., 1951 February-May (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Cunningham, John J., 1951 June-December (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Cunningham, John J., 1952 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Cunningham, John J., 1953 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Cunningham, John J., 1954 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Cunningham, John J., 1955-1957 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Cunningham, John J., 1958-1959 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Cunningham, John J., 1960-1975 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Cunningham, John J., Jr. (of Van Dyke Gallery), 1924-1925 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Curt Valentin Gallery (see Valentin, Curt) (Box 27)
    - Curtis, Charles P., 1939-1943 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Curtis, Cyrus H. K., 1923-1929 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Cushman, Mrs. Charles T., 1962 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Cutten, Mrs. Rudolf E., 1929-1944 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Cutting, Mrs. Charles Suydem, 1937-1948 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Czartoryski, Prince Olgierd, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous C: Cabane-Callatay, 1924-1978 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous C: Calmann-Carey, 1924-1976 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous C: Carlebach-Cartier, 1924-1970 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous C: Carver-Cézanne Memorial Committee, 1925-1965 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous C: Chabaud-Charnace, 1923-1967 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous C: Charvet-Chisholm, 1923-1976 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous C: Chouteau-Clyde, 1923-1972 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous C: Coale-Comité National, 1923-1966 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous C: Committee-Coons, 1923-1963 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous C: Cooper-Courty, 1924-1967 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous C: Cousin-Crocker, 1924-1962 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous C: Cromwell-Curry, 1924-1971 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous C: Curtis-Czinober, 1925-1957 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Daber, Alfred, 1933-1961 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Daehne, Arthur von (see von Daehne, Arthur) (Box 28)
    - Dailey, Lois, 1947-1948 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Dale, Mr. and Mrs. Chester, 1926-1947 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Dalton, Henry G., 1923-1940 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Damiron, S., 1951-1975 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - d'Andria, Ezio, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Danforth, Mrs. Murray S., 1933-1948 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Daniels, David, 1951-1973 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Danielson, Mrs. R. E., 1925-1936 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - David, Henri, 1947-1960 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Davidson, Jo, 1929-1935 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Davies, Marion, 1929-1935 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Davillier, Baron and Baroness, 1955-1957 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Davis, Mr. and Mrs. Arthur V., 1924-1929 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Davis, J. Lionberger, 1924-1930 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Davis, John H., 1954-1958 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Davis, Leopold C., 1929-1934 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Davis, Norman, 1953-1956 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Davis, Richard S., 1958-1969 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Davis, Samuel C., 1925-1938 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Davison, Mrs. H. P., 1928 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Davray, Jean, 1951-1968 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Dawson, H. F., 1923-1937 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Dawson, John W., 1926 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Day & Meyer - Murray & Young, Inc., 1924-1974 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - de Batz, Georges (see also Arnold Seligmann-Helft Corp.), 1940-1946 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - de Batz, Georges (see also Arnold Seligmann-Helft Corp.), 1947-1970 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - de Batz, Georges (see also Arnold Seligmann-Helft Corp.), 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - de Batz, Georges (see also Arnold Seligmann-Helft Corp.), 1973 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - de Batz, Georges (see also Arnold Seligmann-Helft Corp.), 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - de Batz, Georges (see also Arnold Seligmann-Helft Corp.), 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - de Beaufort, Ph. Van Alfen, 1959, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - de Blaas, Guilio and Lulu, 1928-1933 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - de Braux, Georges, 1948-1951 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - de Brisis, le Vicomte, 1954-1955 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - de Broglie, le Duc, 1953-1954 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - de Bueno, Germaine, 1941 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - de Burlet, Ch. Albert, 1954-1957 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - de Chirico, Giorgio, 1937-1939 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - de Coppet, André, 1933-1940 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Decorators Picture Gallery, Inc., 1936-1937 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Decroix, Fernand, 1955-1959 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - de Cuevas, Marquis George, 1932-1943 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - de Demanoix, Comte Henry, 1937-1956 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Deely, Mrs. James S., 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Deering, Charles, 1923-1925 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - de Frey, Dr. Alexander C. (see also de Frey, Mrs. Alexander and von Frey, Dr. Alexander C.), 1946-1947 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - de Frey, Mrs. Alexander (Erika) (see also above entry and von Frey, Dr. Alexander C.), 1958 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - de Giafferri, Monsieur, 1936-1938 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - de Gironde, Comte R. and Comtesse, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - de Goldschmidt-Rothschild, Mrs. R. (Baroness), 1940-1961 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - de Graaff, Jan, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - de Graaff, W. H., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - de Groot, Adelaide, 1936-1940 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - de Gunzburg, Baron Nicolas, 1938-1943 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - De Haspe, André, 1957-1963 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - de Hauke, César M., 1926-1929, 1953-1963 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - de Hevesy, André, 1953-1956 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Dehner, Walt, 1934-1939 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - de Kammerer, Maria, 1932-1955 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - de La Fresnaye, Solange (Solange Sternlicht), 1950-1963 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Delaissé, L.M.J., 1953 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - De Lamar, Alice, 1923-1935 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Delamare, Alexis, 1923-1931 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - De La Rancheraye & Co., 1936-1938 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - de Laroussilhe, Brimo, 1960-1973 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - de la Tour d'Auvergne, Princess, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - de Levaque, Marguerite Marie, 1953-1957 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Delestre, Gaston, 1954-1974 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Delhaye, Alfred, 1969-1973 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - de Limur, Andre and Ethel Mary, 1940-1951 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Dell, Ted, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - Delvaille, G. C. 1973 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Demanoix, Comte Henry de (see de Demanoix, Comte Henry) (Box 29)
    - de Massa, Duc, 1954-1973 (Box 29, Folder 39)
    - de Menil, Jean, 1946-1947 (Box 29, Folder 40)
    - Demeurisse, M. A., 1964 (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - Demogé, Mme. L., 1955 (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - de Molas, Nicholas, 1937-1941 (Box 29, Folder 43)
    - de Montesquiou-Fezensag, le Comte Blaise, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 44)
    - Demotte, Inc., 1921-1932 (Box 29, Folder 45)
    - Demotte, Inc., 1933-1942 (Box 29, Folder 46)
    - de Mouchy, Duchesse, 1953-1954 (Box 29, Folder 47)
    - Denmark-Consulate General, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 48)
    - de Nobele, F. 1956-1973 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Depew, Ganson, 1925-1927 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Dereppe, Gabriel, 1924-1957 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - de Ricci, Seymour, 1923-1938 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Derrick, Robert O., 1926-1938 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - de Schauensee, Baron and Baroness Rudolphe, 1940-1948 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - de Schulthess, Hans, 1941-1947 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Descossy, Michel, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - des Granges, Donald, 1934-1938 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Design Associates, Inc., 1935-1937 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Design Associates, Inc., 1937-1938 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - De Souza, Roberto Pinto, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - De Sylva, B. G., 1938-1946 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - de Talleyrand, Marquis, 1930-1948 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Deutsch, Boris, 1933-1934 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - de Vaux, Baron Maurice, 1927-1933 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - de Veyrac, Marquis Jacques, 1935-1936 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Devigne, Marguerite, 1949-1968 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - de Vries, Henry P., 1948 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - de Walsh-Serrant, Duc, 1954-1955 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - de Wild, Dr. A. Martin, 1953-1955 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - de Wolfe, Elsie, 1923-1936 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Dexter, Mrs. Gordon, 1932-1936 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Dezarrois, André, 1955-1956 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Dickerman, Mrs. Watson B., 1929-1955 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Dillman, Mr. and Mrs. Hugh, 1926-1943 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Dillon, Clarence, 1924-1929 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Directory of Directors Company, 1927-1931 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - di Segni, Leopoldo, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Dodd, J. E., 1935 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Dodge, Mrs. Horace, 1924, 1952 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Dodge, Joseph (Hyde Collection), 1939-1962 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Doig, Wilson & Wheatley, 1934 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Dona dalle Rose, Conte Luigi, 1933-1935 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Donahue, James P., 1923-1936 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Donlon, Thomas, 1925-1938 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Doria, Comte Arnauld, 1952-1960 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Dorr News Service, 1923-1936 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Dorrance, John T., 1926-1932 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Dortu, Mme. Georges, 1938-1950 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Douglas, Mrs. Barclay, 1937-1941 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Douglas, Langston, 1933-1941 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Downing, Mr. and Mrs. John F., 1925-1927 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Downtown Gallery, 1931-1958 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Drack, Walter (see also Bührle, Emil), 1952-1965 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Draper, Mrs. R. S., 1935-1937 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Dreicer, Michael (and Estate of), 1921-1923 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Dreier, Katherine, 1938-1946 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Drey, A. S., 1926-1935 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Drey, F. A., 1943-1950 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Drey, Margaret, 1960-1962 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Drey, Paul, 1931-1953 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Dreyfus, Richard, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Drury, Francis E., 1924-1926 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Dubois, Evelyn, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - du Boisouvray, Count Guy, 1954, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Dubourg, Jacques, 1935-1974 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Dubrujeaud, J., 1937-1949 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Duffy, James F., Jr., 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - du Fontenioux, le Vicomte G. (see Fontenioux, le Vicomte G. du) (Box 31)
    - Dugas, Mlle., 1954-1955 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Duits, Clifford, 1957-1960 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Duits, W. E., 1928-1932 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Duke, Mrs. James B., 1924-1938 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Duke University, 1937 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Dunlap, Charles E., 1939-1964 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - duPont, Alfred I., 1924-1936 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Dupont, Henry F., 1923-1943 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Dupont, Jacques, 1950-1967 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Du Pont, Lammott, 1923-1932 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Durand-Ruel, Inc., 1935-1950 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Durant, W. C., 1925-1929 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Durfey, Frank, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Durlacher Bros., 1926-1954 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Durlacher, George L., 1924-1942 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Durney-Bernsteen, Mme. Monique, 1953-1956 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Dutey-Harispe, 1926-1929 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Duthuit-Matisse, Marguerite, 1949-1950 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Duval, Paul, 1956-1961 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Duveen Brothers, Inc., 1928-1954 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Dwight, Voorhis & Helmsley, Inc., 1940-1945 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Dyer, George R., 1936-1948 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous D: D-Danielson, 1924-1975 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous D: Dargnies-Decour, 1923-1970 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous D: Dedrick-Delforge, 1925-1965 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous D: Dellett-Desclaux, 1924-1969 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous D: Desjardins-De Wolfe, 1925-1973 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous D: Dhainaut-di Zoppola, 1923-1966 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous D: Dobbins-Donnelly, 1925-1970 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous D: Dorn-Doyle, 1923-1967 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous D: Drake-Drutman, 1925-1962 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous D: Du-Dunseith, 1924-1978 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous D: Dupont-Dyer, 1923-1957 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - E. L. Hildreth & Co., 1939 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Earl, Maud, 1927-1928 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Eastman, George, 1924-1929 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Easton, Linwood, 1934-1935 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Eccles, Dr. George W., 1931-1936 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Ederheimer, Richard, 1925-1942 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Edinburg, Mrs. Joseph M., 1958-1971 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Editions Aimery Somogy, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Edmiston, Rodman W., 1934-1938 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Edwards, Edward W., 1924-1940 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Edwards, R. J., 1925-1928 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Edwards, W. Neilson, 1930-1936 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Ehret, Mr. and Mrs. George, Jr., 1923-1927 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Ehret, Mrs. Louis J., 1927-1930 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Ehrich Galleries, 1932-1935 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Ehrlich, Alfred, 1939 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Ehrman, Mrs. Ernest, 1926-1927 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Ehrman, Mrs. Sidney M., 1923-1938 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Ehrmann, Jean, 1949-1969 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Eichholz, Robert B., 1944-1950 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Eisendrath, William, Jr., 1943-1952 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Eisner, Isidore, 1926-1929 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Eisner, Mr. and Mrs. Mark, 1938-1939 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Eissler, Dr. Herman and Hortense, 1940-1964 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Eitner, Lorenz, undated (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Elbert, Mrs. Robert G., 1929-1936 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Electrical Testing Laboratories, Inc., 1943 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Elizabethan Club, 1939 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Elkins, Frances A., 1938-1941 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Elkins, George W., 1924-1948 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Elkins, Mrs. William, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Ellis, Theodore T., 1932-1933 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Elsen, Albert, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Emery, Thomas J. and J. J., 1925-1946 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Empire Trust Company, 1924-1927 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Employment Correspondence File, 1935-1966, (4 folders; not scanned) (Box 34, Folder 1-4)
    - Endicott, Col. W., 1924-1929 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Enos, Mrs. E. A., 1924-1929 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Epstein, Jacob, 1923-1936 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Epstein, Max, 1923-1944 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Erbach-Erbach, Frans Graf zu, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Erbe, Gustav, Jr., 1934-1937 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Erich S. Hermann, Inc., 1941-1948 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Erickson, A. W. 1926-1950 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Erickson, Colonel H., 1930-1931 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Erlanger, Arthur L., 1932-1958 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Erlanger, Phillippe, 1955-1959 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Ernest Brown & Phillips, Ltd., 1933-1935 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Ernould-Gandouet, Marielle, 1965-1966 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Ernst, Rudolf J., 1941-1977 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Errera, Mrs. Jacqueline, 1941-1942 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Escholier, Mme. Raymond, 1954-1959 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Esherick, Wharton, 1934-1936 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Esnault-Pelterie, Robert, 1949-1954 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Estrangin, Henri, 1941-1946 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - European Correspondence Logs, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - European Correspondence Logs, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - European Correspondence Logs, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Exton, Manning P. M., 1936-1975 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous E: Earley-Edwards, 1925-1963 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous E: Eeckhout-Eisler, 1927-1969 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous E: Elbogen-Encyclopedia Britannica, 1923-1978 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous E: Endicott-Erlanger, 1925-1963 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous E: Ernst-Eyraud, 1924-1962 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - F. A. Bernett Books, 1954-1956 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - F. Kleinberger Galleries, Inc., 1921-1929 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - F. Kleinberger Galleries, Inc., 1929 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - F. L. Kraemer & Co., 1935-1952 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Fabius Frères, 1949-1950 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Fagothey, James, 1940 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Fahnestock, William, 1925-1933 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Falcke Art Association, 1935-1936 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Falcke, Capt. Shirley, 1934 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Farago, Joseph, 1938-1973 (Box 35, Folder 19)